https://www.reliantbank.com/privacy-policy/

Important changes to the Secure Login Box
To login to Online Banking beginning Nov. 17, click or tap “Log in”, and then enter your username and password on the next page. Click HERE for more information.
Important changes to the Secure Login Box
To login to Business Online Banking beginning Nov. 17, click or tap “Log in”, and then enter your username and password on the next page. Click HERE for more information.
If you have been financially impacted by Hurricane Laura and are concerned about your ability to maintain your upcoming loan payment, please click here.
If you are a Registered User select “Manufactured Home Registered User”
To pay as a Guest, select “Manufactured Home Pay as Guest”
Online Banking
Business Online Banking
Credit Card
Mortgage
Login target
Log in
New user? Register for online banking.
Forgot ID or Password?
Log in
Lost or Damaged Token
Forgot password or PIN?
Log in
Need assistance with your credit card? Call 1-855-401-4743, or click here.
Manufactured Home Registered User
Manufactured Home Pay as Guest
Log in
Welcome to Reliant Bank! For more information on making your payment, click here.
Search
Search
Privacy Policy
For California Residents interested in exercising their rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act, please click to complete a personal information request.
Click Here
Below is the current Privacy Policy for Reliant Bank.  If you wish to receive a printed copy, please call 1-877-221-2050.
Rev. 01/2018
FACTS
WHAT DOES RELIANT BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security Number and Income
Account Balances and Payment History
Credit Scores and Transaction History
When you are no longer our customer, we may continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Reliant Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Reliant Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
No
We Don’t Share
For our affiliates’ to market you
No
We Don’t Share
For nonaffiliates’ to market to you
No
We Don’t Share
What we do
How does Reliant Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Reliant Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an Account or Apply for a Loan
Deposit Money or Provide you Mortgage Information
Show your Driver’s License
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates’ from using your information to market to you
Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.
Our affiliates include financial companies such as Reliant Bancorp, Inc., which is the bank's parent company.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.
Reliant Bank does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include investment services and credit card companies
Questions?
© 2020 Reliant Bank. All Rights Reserved.
